# **Justin Perry**

## Junior Front-end Developer

Washington, PA 15301 justin.taylor.perry@gmail.com +1 724 344 7324

Hardworking Junior Front-end Developer bringing 3 + years of experience performing diverse troubleshooting, maintenance, and repair skills. Experienced in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

### **Apartment Maintenance Technician**

Prudential Realty Company - Washington, PA January 2020 to Present

Rehabilitated over 25 apartment units.

Worked frequently with mechanical and plumbing systems to complete knowledgeable inspections and skilled repairs.

Used various equipment to remove snow and sprinkled rock salt on walkways to prevent falls.

Finalized work on building systems by completing basic carpentry and other finish work.

Completed partial or full dismantling of equipment to quickly repair or replace defective components and restore functionality.

Quickly responded to internal service calls regarding malfunctioning equipment and completed repairs. Installed new locks, door handles and door closers.

Removed outdoor debris and yard clippings into receptacles to properly maintain grounds.

Worked with building managers to assess ongoing needs and plan preventive maintenance and cleaning schedules.

Checked for storm damage around property and contacted supervisor with findings.

Used problem-solving skills to alleviate issues efficiently with minimal supervision.

Inspected fire extinguisher equipment on state-mandated schedule.

Examined alarm systems and monitors to meet fire marshal standards and safeguard personnel.

Toured property with prospective tenants and provided wealth of information in regards to its key features.

Participated in property inspections to prepare for move-ins and move-outs.

#### **Apartment Maintenance Technician**

Cedarcove Capital Ventures - Pittsburgh, PA December 2017 to January 2019

Rehabilitated over 25 townhouse units.

Carried out building updates such as painting surfaces, replacing fixtures and reorganizing rooms.

Inspected buildings, grounds and equipment for unsafe or malfunctioning conditions.

Used standard housekeeping equipment, tools and supplies to accomplish basic cleaning.

Worked quickly on emergency requests in order to minimize disruptions to operations.

Followed instructions from supervisor regarding daily job tasks and duties.

Reported issues to property manager so effective resolutions could be put into place.

Positively engaged with customers and maintained professional appearance as company representative.

## Education

## **High School Diploma**

Pymatuning Valley High School - Andover, OH August 2013 to May 2017

#### Skills

- Computer skills (5 years)
- IT support (2 years)
- HTML5 (5 years)
- CSS (5 years)
- JavaScript (5 years)
- Troubleshooting
- Calculus (2 years)

#### Assessments

#### **Verbal communication — Proficient**

March 2022

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely

Full results: Proficient

## **Sales skills — Proficient**

March 2022

Influencing and negotiating with customers

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.